globalwolfweb.com 2011-06-11

# Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies

**Overview**  
Most of the information accessible on the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s website does not require you to identify yourself at all. You may access it anonymously. However, Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. does collect personal information about you when you choose to provide it. We endeavour to collect only as much personal information as is absolutely necessary to assist you in conducting business with Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. via the website.

**Purposes for which we collect Personal Information**  
We collect and retain personal information for the following purposes:

  * To process your requests for services, products or further information
  * To communicate with you regarding services or products that you have requested 
  * To identify you if you have a query or concern about the service or product that you have requested
  * To advise you about changes to our web service offerings and of service interruptions
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements
  * Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If your personal information changes (eg. name, address, postal code, telephone number, etc.), or you no longer desire our services, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove this information. Details of how to do this are usually provided on the web page where the information is collected or displayed.

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**  
Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on its site. We do not use or retain personal information that you provide to us for any secondary purposes unless we clearly notify you and gain your permission first. We will not sell, share, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to any organization or individual outside Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. unless we first notify you and ask your permission. The exceptions to this policy of non-disclosure are stated below. Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. may disclose your personal information:

  * To companies contracted to process your requests
  * For law enforcement purposes

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may occasionally report aggregated demographic information in the form of reports and statistics but this is not linked to any personal information that can be used to identify any individual person.

Some of the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s sub-systems require the use of "cookies". For example, we use cookies when you logon over the Internet to save the contents of your work as you proceed from one screen to another. Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. uses "per-session" cookies only. Per-session cookies are small files that are temporarily stored in your computer's memory and are deleted when you leave the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s web site.

**Protection of Personal Information**  
Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. takes every precaution to protect your personal information on the Internet. We protect your account information by requiring you to enter a unique Login ID and Password each time you want to access your account information. Your Password should never be shared with anyone.

Questions about the collection of personal information should be directed to the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s Privacy Coordinator.  Email, phone and mail addresses can be found below.  

Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. uses SSL encryption technology to protect personal information (eg. credit card numbers, etc.) during transmission. A security icon will appear in your browser window to indicate that you are using a secure site.  

If you have any questions or concerns about the security at our website, you can send an email to [webmaster@lwolf.com](mailto:webmaster@lwolf.com)  

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns, please contact the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s Privacy Coordinator.

**Privacy Coordinator Contact**  
Email: [privacy@lwolf.com](mailto:privacy@lwolf.com)

Telephone: (519)624-1236  

Mail:  
Privacy Coordinator  
Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.  
231 Shearson Cres, Suite 310  
Cambridge, ON  N1T1J5

**Notification of Changes to the Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s home page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  

**Links to Other Websites**  
The Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s website contains links to other sites (eg. business links, etc.). Please be aware that Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc. cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. When you leave our site, we encourage you to read the privacy statement of each and every website that you visit before you provide any personal information. The Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s privacy statement applies solely to information collected on the Lone Wolf Real Estate Technologies Inc.'s website.
